[
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:11 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "C0DEED",
    "color": "C91C8D",
    "question": "Why did I just buy an android charger 🙄?",
    "textB": "RT @HowardKurtz: Wikileaks makes top of P. 1 at NYT, WP, WSJ, top of CBS &amp; NBC newscasts.Sudden surge because now about Hill &amp; Bill https:/\u2026 ",
    "screenName": "dasiat__",
    "nameB": "ron headley",
    "answer": "because now about Hill &amp; Bill ",
    "credits": "By Muffin and ron headley.",
    "by": "Muffin & ron headley",
    "name": "Muffin",
    "text": "Why did I just buy an android charger 🙄 ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:15 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "getronheadley"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:03 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "F5F8FA",
    "color": "FF6699",
    "question": "Why did she make the comments?",
    "textB": "Because your kisses make my lips quiver.\n\n&amp; when you touch me, my whole body shiver ",
    "screenName": "lissasno1fan",
    "nameB": "Theyloveicey",
    "answer": "Because your kisses make my lips quiver.\n\n&amp; when you touch me, my whole body shiver",
    "credits": "By Lissa Merriman and Theyloveicey.",
    "by": "Lissa Merriman & Theyloveicey",
    "name": "Lissa Merriman",
    "text": "@hille422 Why did she make the comments? ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:15 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "TheyLoveIceyy"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:55 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "000000",
    "color": "F5F8FA",
    "question": "why did I fucking think that I would be okay with drawing him?",
    "textB": "Nah because powerhouse got me sounding like somebody smoked out aunty ",
    "screenName": "americansunsets",
    "nameB": "Ness Dukes",
    "answer": "because powerhouse got me sounding like somebody smoked out aunty",
    "credits": "By k8y k8 and Ness Dukes.",
    "by": "k8y k8 & Ness Dukes",
    "name": "k8y k8",
    "text": "why did I fucking think that I would be okay with drawing him ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:15 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "___Nesssaaa"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:53 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "C0DEED",
    "color": "C0DEED",
    "question": "Why did you rush off soooo fast 😐🙈🙄😂 @FreddyParker98?",
    "textB": "I will wait for you because honestly l don't want anyone else 💕 https://t.co/jo53JZnqB3 ",
    "screenName": "CharlotteBleak2",
    "nameB": "Александра",
    "answer": "because honestly l don't want anyone else 💕 ",
    "credits": "By Charlotte ✌️ and Александра.",
    "by": "Charlotte ✌️ & Александра",
    "name": "Charlotte ✌️",
    "text": "Why did you rush off soooo fast 😐🙈🙄😂 @FreddyParker98 ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:15 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "sashka_mm"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:51 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "000000",
    "color": "131516",
    "question": "Why did I just find out they locked up the goat?",
    "textB": "RT @Truthbytony: If Ciara is a hoe because she fell in love, got married, then had a baby what's your mother ? https://t.co/9gGaBnmtVc ",
    "screenName": "kylerandall08",
    "nameB": "bby",
    "answer": "because she fell in love, got married, then had a baby what's your mother ? ",
    "credits": "By Kyle and bby.",
    "by": "Kyle & bby",
    "name": "Kyle",
    "text": "Why did I just find out they locked up the goat??? #FreeFlock \u203c️\u203c️\u203c️ ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:15 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "love_youuuuu__"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:49 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "F5F8FA",
    "color": "FFFFFF",
    "question": "Why did it just hit me rn that he's gonna become our next president?",
    "textB": "RT @wh_honeytree: Don't leave my side,\nBecause in a world without you, there is no me. https://t.co/3tgsHHa9le ",
    "screenName": "kxshley",
    "nameB": "Baby_hyun",
    "answer": "Because in a world without you, there is no me. ",
    "credits": "By jess  🦄 and Baby_hyun.",
    "by": "jess  🦄 & Baby_hyun",
    "name": "jess  🦄",
    "text": "Why did it just hit me rn that he's gonna become our next president? ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "baby_hyun91"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:47 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "FFFFFF",
    "color": "000000",
    "question": "Why did we fuck up as a nation and have Clinton and Trump as our candidates?",
    "textB": "RT @FemaleTexts: I'm sad that vine is closing down because where else will you find videos like this https://t.co/WZFKurSlpS ",
    "screenName": "justcallmeAl_1",
    "nameB": "24k Mare✨",
    "answer": "because where else will you find videos like this ",
    "credits": "By al and 24k Mare✨.",
    "by": "al & 24k Mare✨",
    "name": "al",
    "text": "Why did we fuck up as a nation and have Clinton and Trump as our candidates? ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "Stillsaucinmare"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:42 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "000000",
    "color": "F5F8FA",
    "question": "why did katappa kill bahubali ?",
    "textB": "Love that the male contraceptive needs more work because of side effects such as depression and acne... euh.. Isn't that what females get? ",
    "screenName": "Neeraj29779125",
    "nameB": "ThatLipstickLife",
    "answer": "because of side effects such as depression and acne",
    "credits": "By Neeraj sarwan and ThatLipstickLife.",
    "by": "Neeraj sarwan & ThatLipstickLife",
    "name": "Neeraj sarwan",
    "text": "RT @iJayHR: @iHrithik why did katappa kill bahubali ??\n#TeamKaabilLive ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "thatlipsticklif"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:42 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "C0DEED",
    "color": "C0DEED",
    "question": "why did I actually say this the other day ?",
    "textB": "i'm about to start selling my Pee because pee because people need to pass drink test &amp; people know i don't smoke or drink lmfao ",
    "screenName": "jay_flemmy",
    "nameB": "ShΔ'CΔRRIΘ KΣllΣY ϟ",
    "answer": "because pee because people need to pass drink test &amp; people know i don't smoke or drink lmfao",
    "credits": "By Jordyn (with a y) and ShΔ'CΔRRIΘ KΣllΣY ϟ.",
    "by": "Jordyn (with a y) & ShΔ'CΔRRIΘ KΣllΣY ϟ",
    "name": "Jordyn (with a y)",
    "text": "💀💀💀why did I actually say this the other day https://t.co/BQ4KrXLrHZ ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "Luffy_Sexx"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:41 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "131516",
    "color": "C0DEED",
    "question": "why did this remind me of you 😂?",
    "textB": "RT @FreeBeacon: \u201cYou do it because it\u2019s right.\u201d https://t.co/SJfh6EKYxb https://t.co/Yz6oSrwczy ",
    "screenName": "AddieHawk04",
    "nameB": "toughguy1967",
    "answer": "because it\u2019s right.\u201d ",
    "credits": "By addie hawk and toughguy1967.",
    "by": "addie hawk & toughguy1967",
    "name": "addie hawk",
    "text": "@BestHairstyIes @lydiarobertssss why did this remind me of you 😂 ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "toughguy1967"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:33 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "F5F8FA",
    "color": "C0DEED",
    "question": "Why did you do that to me\" original version! \nTae: Listen to it with your eyes closed and cameras turned off~?",
    "textB": "I'd pleas the 5th as well, because anything else implicates her in the future. This corruption is just ridiculous a\u2026 https://t.co/uOwDs8LOZM ",
    "screenName": "_vEHEHv_",
    "nameB": "DeplorableTim",
    "answer": "because anything else implicates her in the future. This corruption is just ridiculous a\u2026 ",
    "credits": "By 💉💦😭 and DeplorableTim.",
    "by": "💉💦😭 & DeplorableTim",
    "name": "💉💦😭",
    "text": "RT @jeongmilk: LRT ㅋㅋㅋ\nJM: \"Why did you do that to me\" original version! \nTae: Listen to it with your eyes closed and cameras turned off~ ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "OhioTim3629"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:30 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "C0DEED",
    "color": "000000",
    "question": "Why did you have to leave me?",
    "textB": "People may be annoyed with you today because your behavior is ... More for Aquarius https://t.co/rOtXo4zBdk ",
    "screenName": "EzraTero",
    "nameB": "Shana Thompson",
    "answer": "because your behavior is ",
    "credits": "By EZRA and Shana Thompson.",
    "by": "EZRA & Shana Thompson",
    "name": "EZRA",
    "text": "RT @kennysamoza: Why did you have to leave me? ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "shana_laniece"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:28 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "1C130E",
    "color": "000000",
    "question": "Why did I do this to myself?",
    "textB": "Okay. I need sleep. Waking up in like 7 hours to shower and then go into the city because someone is back from France... ",
    "screenName": "JenSanchezArt",
    "nameB": "SHINee back in Nov.",
    "answer": "because someone is back from France",
    "credits": "By SpookyJen and SHINee back in Nov..",
    "by": "SpookyJen & SHINee back in Nov.",
    "name": "SpookyJen",
    "text": "I made a mistake. I really wanted a strawberry milkshake and now my stomach hurts. Why did I do this to myself? #lactoseintolerant #owie ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "solarmoonmoo"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:27 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "C0DEED",
    "color": "000000",
    "question": "why did i think of @aleshaxbreezy ?",
    "textB": "RT @BethWeber1: How about 1,000 retweets 4 this because we've had enough of the lies, bigotry, misogyny. The hatred.\nBecause we the people\u2026 ",
    "screenName": "ChrisMcCullyTv",
    "nameB": "Just Red",
    "answer": "because we've had enough of the lies, bigotry, misogyny. The hatred.\nBecause we the people\u2026",
    "credits": "By spooky chris 🎃 and Just Red.",
    "by": "spooky chris 🎃 & Just Red",
    "name": "spooky chris 🎃",
    "text": "why did i think of @aleshaxbreezy https://t.co/GEklg8nnek ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "JoyToy312"
  },
  {
    "date": "Fri Oct 28 17:03:24 +0000 2016",
    "colorB": "C0DEED",
    "color": "C0DEED",
    "question": "Why did everyone in the building decide to do their laundry rn🙃?",
    "textB": "RT @ReIatableThings: *removes the emoji next to ur name because u dont mean shit to me anymore* ",
    "screenName": "AllisonKropf",
    "nameB": "jenna bean",
    "answer": "because u dont mean shit to me anymore*",
    "credits": "By Allison and jenna bean.",
    "by": "Allison & jenna bean",
    "name": "Allison",
    "text": "Why did everyone in the building decide to do their laundry rn🙃 ",
    "dateB": "Fri Oct 28 17:04:14 +0000 2016",
    "screenNameB": "_jennie_09"
  }
]